Fear is just a word. Reality is much worse.
Grave Encounters 2 is a horror film directed by John Poliquin.
Tortured by the ghosts of the demonized insane asylum that killed the crew of GRAVE ENCOUNTERS, film students fight
to escape death as their own paranormal investigation goes terribly wrong in this horrifying sequel.
Alex Wright, played by Richard Harmon.
Tessa Hamill, played by Stephanie Bennett.
Lance Preston, played by Sean Rogerson.
Trevor Thompson, played by Dylan Playfair.
Jennifer Parker, played by Leanne Lapp.
Jared Lee, played by Howie Lai.
Grave Encounters 2 is a 2012 Canadian found footage supernatural horror film
written by the Vicious Brothers and directed by John Poliquin.
The sequel to Grave Encounters (2011), it stars Richard Harmon, Leanne Lapp, Dylan Playfair, Stephanie Bennett, and Howard Lai as a group of fans of the original Grave Encounters film who break
into the same psychiatric hospital where the film took place to investigate whether its events were real and find themselves terrorized by the hospital's malevolent entities.
The film utilizes metafictional and film within a film elements as Sean Rogerson plays a fictional
version of himself who reprises his role as Lance Preston from the original film.
Grave Encounters 2 was released on iTunes on October 2, 2012, with a limited
theatrical release in the United States, on October 12, 2012.
The film was a commercial success, grossing over $8.2 million against a $1.4 million budget,
but unlike its predecessor, it received generally negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of insanity,
supernatural, halloween, haunting, dormitory.
The tone is dark.